Pham Dinh Triet

Full Stack Developer Phone: 0799698143

Website: https://trietpham96.github.io/mycv/

Email: trietpham96@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/đinh-triết-pham-2b992a160

SUMMARY

I'm a full stack developer with 3 years of experience in AngularJS, C#.NET, with knowledge of Front-End Web Development (AngularJS), RESTful API, Entity Code First, Linq to Entity, Repository Patterns and Database Design.

Coding, learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I am considered a team-player because I like to help other and tend to work well within the group.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- C#.NET, JavaScript, TypeScript
- HTML, CSS

Frameworks/ Platforms:

- AngularJS, Angular2+, NodeJS
- GulpJS
- WebAPI, RestfulAPI, JSON
- Entity CodeFirst, Ling to Entity
- jQuery, Twitter Bootstrap

Database:

Microsoft SQL

IDE:

- Visual Studio 2017
- Visual Studio Code

Version Control:

- Git (Github), SVN

Foreign Languages:

English:

Communicate: ordinaryRead & write: average

Soft Skills:

- Time management
- Teamwork
- Business communication

EDUCATION

Cao Thang Technical colleges

- Studying Software Engineering
- Degree grade: Good

From 2014 to 2017

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SystemGear Viet Nam

11/2017 - Now

Position: Full Stack Developer

• **Project:** BestGear Transportation Management.

• **Project Description**: Logistics software for container management

http://www.bestgear-series.com/

Team Size: 10Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers and teammates to clarify requirement. Design UX/UI and implement the solution (both back-end and front-end) based on the requirements.

Deploy to server and monitor system stability.

Division of tasks, mentoring and do code reviews for other team members.

Ferya Software 1/2017 – 11/2017

Position: Software Engineer

• Project:

https://sulily.vn/ https://silamp.vn/

https://phumyhung.vn/midtown/

Team Size: 5

Responsibilities:

Graduation internship and become a full time employee, participating in the company's web projects.

Design database, front-end and back-end programming of web mobile projects and deploy server, develop and fix the application's defect base on requirement, prepare document and technical guide for developers joining in the middle of the project.

Write key technical documents and mentor new members of the team.

Collaborate with team leader to define and improve the team's workflow.

PASTIMES AND ACTIVITIES

- I am keen on reading books, IT blogs, Medium, and Quora in my free time.
- My other hobby is gym, soccer and music.